A hot mess, hot mess
息吹きかけて Listen up
とびきり“らしさ”で Fill it up
Iʼm a troublemaker, troublemaker Yuh!
Whatʼs so funny, funny, honey?
I got Ahh your attention
Sing loud, loud
Sing loud, loud loud loud
あっという間に Time’s up
Open your blind blind mind mind
Everybody waits for me
Make the sensation
どんな形でも Okay Okay
ひたすら On my way
Take it slowly
Ainʼt no worry
Dancing with the flames
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD Hwi Hwi
I am the one (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
止まらない もう
I am the one (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
画期的登場シーン
Shake it Mix it 目を惹く My style
目が眩むほど光る Dimension
Feel it coming now,
feel it taking over
I’ll blow ur mind mind like all the time time
潜めた ænergy 夢のDesigner
Now, Now oh yeah, that’s right right
So come on
いつも攻めてる Show you ma attitude
どんな形でも Okay
ひたすら On my way
Take it slowly
Ainʼt no worry
Dancing with the flames
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD
I never lay low, never lay low
U watch me glow glow,
watch me glow glow
Drama has begun This is not fiction
Ready or Not
Make it hot hot, make it hot hot
Baby Iʼm on fire, Iʼm on fire
Fire Ah Ooh
I'm a hot mess, hot mess
描いてきた Story Never hesitate
So if U LIKE it,
I can take you to MY WORLD
I am the one (Hot)
I am the best (Hot)
止まらない もう (I am the one)
I am the one (Hot)
And now my turn (Hot)
Yeah, Iʼm a hot mess
Know you want it some more
時空を飛び越え Believe in yourself
開かれた世界
Hot mess, hot mess